Week1
We formed a group, and chose the project P24.

Week2
We discussed about the project work. And learnt about the background of the project. Review the knowledge we learnt before.

Week3
Meeting with the client on Wednesday morning. And discussed how to write the proposal.

Week4
Design some API for backend.

Week5
Meeting with the client and ask the question with the BP database we are facing.

Week6
Continue to work on the project and fixing the database issue.

Week7
Almost finish the requirements for connecting with frontend and backend.

Week8
Totally complete the query function in database which require from client.

Week9
Finish more functions for adding, deleting and changing with the database.

Week10 
complete the project and make the final demo. Working on the report. 